A Guide to the Lilla Richards Collection, 1914-2016 (bulk 1970-2001)
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 6: Fairfax County Planning Files, 1957-2013
  - Sub-series 6-3: Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1957-2002
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1977, 77-D-057, Julian M. Dillard, McLean CBD, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1977, 77-D-083, Barbara A. May, Evermay Subdivision, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1977-1978, 77-D-039 and 77-D-100, Dorsey W. Rohrbaugh and Wheeler B. Santmyer, 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1977-1978, 77-D-43, Charles Bassing, 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1977-1978, 77-D-103, Dittmar Company, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1977-1978, 77-D-116, Peter L. Lowenfield, McLean CBD, 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1978, 78-D-010, Raymond V. Raehn, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1978, 78-D-021, Diane Von Meister (Includes cases Clarence A. Ashley III 77-D-052 and Creative Associates 76-D-089), 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1978, 78-D-034, MSC Partnerships (Miller/Smith/Coston) McLean CBD, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1977, 78-W-139, Various Districts, Board of Supervisors' Own Motion, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1978, SC-86-78, Charlotte T. Corner - Dr. George Murnan, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1978-1979, 78-D-099, Evans North, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1979-1980, 79-D-047, Joseph H. Rosenbaum, 1979-1980 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1980, RZ 80-L-103, Woodbury Woods Associates, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1980-1981, RZ 80-D-087, ASR Associates, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1980, RZ 80-D-117, James S. Albritain, Trustee, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1981, 81-II-12M, L. Dail for McLean Citizens Association, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1981, 81-II-V3, Board of Supervisors, West side of Emerson Avenue, south side of Chain Bridge Road and North of Lowell Ave., 1981 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1981, 81-II-7V and 81-II-8M, W. Sherman and Wessynton Development Company, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1981, RZ 81-D-003, Whittier Avenue Joint Venture, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1981, RZ 81-D-024, Rozansky and Kay Construction Company, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1981, SE 81-D-10, John E. Termini, McLean CBC, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1981, SE 81-D-23, Robert L. Hearne, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1981, SE 81-D-030, Harvery Cherner, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1981, SE 81-D-033, Shell Oil Company, McLean CBD, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1981, SE 81-D-039, Hills Nursery West, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1981, SE 81-D-43, R. A. Vinzant and W. L. Wood, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1981, SE 81-D-068 M. B. Imports, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1981, SC 81-D-107, B. F. Saul Investment Trust, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1982, SE 82-D-096, William R. McAteer, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1982, 81-D-079, Lawrence Boehly and Robert A. Young, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1982, 81-P-080, John G. Georgelas, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1983, A-83-D-006, Capper's Nursery, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1983, SE-83-D-016 and TM 30-2, Roy Rogers/Marriott Corporation. McLean CBD, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1983, SE 83-D-041, The Brandywine Group (R. Young Office, Ingleside), 1983 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1983, SE 83-D-106 and PCA 84-D-009-1, F. Fremont Day, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1983, 83-D-102, Kim Antiques, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1983, SP1141, Elm Street Offices, McLean CBD, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1983-1984, 83-II-2M, Nye Property/Woodside, 1983-1984 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1983-1984, 83-D-080, Robert A. Young Associates, 1983-1984 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1983-1985, SP 85-D-060, The Courts, 1983-1985 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1984, SE-83-D-104, Advanced Mobile Phone, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1984, SE 84-D-003, First American Bank, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1984, SC 84-D-017, Anthony Tsitos, McLean CBD, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1984, SE 84-D-029 and SE 84-D-065. McLean Savings & Loan Association; Young & O'Meara; Dolly Madison Partnership, McLean CBD, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1984, SE 84-D-087, Gulf Oil Corporation, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1984-1985, SE 84-D-127, Texaco, Inc., McLean CBD, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1985, APR 85-II-1M, Hazelton Laboratories, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1985, SE 85-D-019, McLean Bible Church Property, Lewinsville, 1985-2002 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1985, PCA A-194-2, Robert A. Young Associates, and 80-D-050 Curran Square, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1985, SP 85-D-048, Shiloh Baptist Church/Odricks, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1985, 85-D-039, Rucker Reality, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1985, SE 85-D-48, Old Chain Bridge Road Associates. (Includes SE 84-D-133 and Compson Development brochure), 1985 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1985, SE 85-D-066, Mobil Oil, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1985, SPA 72-D-007-2, Buena Vista, and RZ 85-D-03 1, Tennis Club, McLean CBD, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1985, VC 85-D-089, Kontzias Flower Shop, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1985-1986, SE 85-D-096, Technical Roof, 1985-1986 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1985-1986, SE 85-D-129, Edward Koepenik, 1985-1986 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1985-1986, SC 85-D-146, Laughlin House/"Blue House" McLean CBD, 1985-1986 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1985-1986, SP 1985-?-? McLean Baptist Church, 1985-1986 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1986-1987, SC 86-D-079, Robert A. Young Associates, 1986-1987 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1986-1987, SC 86-D-080, Robert A. Young Associates, 1986-1987 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1986, SE 86-D-142, Karloid/Hazelton Labortories, 1975, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 1987, S86-II-M1, Vinson Hall Expansion, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Applications, 2000, SE-00-D-007, Providence Baptist Church, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Dranesville District Site Plan Waiver/Entrance Modification, Bruce E. Kelly & Company Realtors Driveway Issue, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Dranesville District Rezoning Controversy - Alan I. Kay Property; Reflection Lake and Autumn Glen subdivisions; Rock Hill Road area, 1990-1992 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Dranesville District Zoning Case, 2001, 2232-D01-23 AT&T Stealth Monopole, Old Dominion Drive, Zbigniew Brzezinski and Others, 2000-2002 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Great Falls Area of Dranesville District - Correspondence, 1964-2008 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Great Falls Area of Dranesville District - Crippen Landfill ("Stump Dump" on Utterback Store Road), 1979-1988 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Great Falls Area of Dranesville District - Gift Lots Issue, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Great Falls Area of Dranesville District - Newspaper Clippings, 1967-1991 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Herndon Area of Dranesville District - Correspondence and Newspaper Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Personal Binder on Great Falls Issues (maintained by Lilla Richards as Dranesville District Supervisor), 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Sub-series 6-4: McLean Subdivision Files, 1970-2013
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - Ballantrae, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - Beverly Manor, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - Bryn Mawr, ca. 1981 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - Chesterbrook Woods, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - The Colonies, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - Evermay, 1975-1986 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - Franklin Area, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - Greenway Heights, 1985 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - Holly Hills, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - Kenmore (Court Case: Board of Supervisors of Fairfax County vs. Ahmad and Nafiesa Khatib), 1991 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - Kent Gardens, 1978, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - Langley Oaks and Earlier Proposed Langley Golf Course, 1973-1988 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - McLean Country Estates, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - McLean Hamlet, 1974-1978 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - McLean Knolls, 1976-1977 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - Odrick's Corner, 1970-2006 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - Old Chesterbrook Village, 1974-1977 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - Rocky Run (Part 1), 1974-1976 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - Rocky Run (Part 2), 1974-1976 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - West McLean, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - Windy Hill, 1974-1991 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Lilla Richards' Files on McLean Subdivisions - Woodside, 1974-1991 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Dranesville District Council of Citizens Associations (By-laws, Correspondence, "What's Happening in Dranesville?" Newsletter), 1974-1983 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Dranesville District Subdivisions - Colvin Mill Gardens (Court Case: William Hamilton, et al. vs. Fairfax County Board of Supervisors), 1989 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Dranesville District Subdivisions - Holly Knolls - Cup Leaf Holly Court (personal notes), 1988 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Dranesville District Subdivisions - Ridgegate Woods (Plat Map), 1987 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Dranesville District - Springvale Community Planning Sector, 2013 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Spring Hill Recreation Center and Pool Dedication [photos], 1988-1990 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Sub-series 6-5: Tysons Corner Files, 1962-2006
    - Tysons Corner - Newspaper Clippings, 1962-2006 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Tysons Corner - Tysons 1963 Aerial Images, 1965 Comprehensive Land Use Plan Map, 1963, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Tysons Corner - Highlights of Tysons Corner Area, 1965? (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Tysons Corner - Tysons Corner Traffic Circulation (Documents and Maps), 1972-1977 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1972 (Contains maps), 1972 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1973, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1974, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1975 (Contains maps), 1975 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1975 - Tysons Area Study Task Force, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1976 (Contains maps), 1976 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1976 - Tysons Area Study Task Force, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1976 - Tysons Corner Urban Design Charette, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1977 - Tysons Corner Study Area Task Force, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1977 - Tysons Corner Area Study, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1977 - Tysons II Materials (Contains maps), 1977 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1977 - Westpark, 1977-1980 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1977 - Tysons Corner Map (4 copies; one is annotated in color), 1977 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1977 - Tysons Corner Circulation Plan, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1978-1979 - Control Data Site, Agreements, & Covenants, 1978-1981 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1980 - Tysons Corner Sheraton Rezoning Case and Related Documents, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1981 - Tysons II Newspaper Clippings, 1977-1981 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1982 - Westpark Rezoning Applications, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1984 - Tysons II Newspaper Clippings, 1975-1984 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1984-1985 - Rezoning, SE 85-D-028 Rouse & Associates Tysons Corner - Increase in Building Height and Eating Establishment, 1984-1985 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1985 - T-Cas Properties, Inc., Application to Increase Building Height, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1985-1986 - Tysons I Changes Planned (Includes Tysons Corner Center store directory), 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1989 - BuildAmerica Three Board of Directors Minutes, 1989 April 24 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Tysons Corner - Washington Post Newspaper Articles featuring Lilla Richards, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1990 - Tysons Corner Task Force, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 1991 - Tysons Corner Task Force, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 2000 - Land Unit S Tysons Corner Urban Center, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 2001 - Clippings on Tysons Corner, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Tysons Corner - Documents for 2001 - Tysons Corner APR Nominations, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Tysons Corner - Tycon Tower - Studies, Plans, and Clippings (Rezoning Cases RZ 79-D-141; SE 80-D-057) (Includes an undated map by Tycon, "Tysons Corner Map"), 1981 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Tysons Corner - Tycon Tower - Studies, Plans, and Clippings, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Tysons Corner - Tycon Tower - Studies, Plans, and Clippings, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Tysons Corner - Tycon Tower - Promotional Folder by Tycon Developers, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Tysons Corner - Tycon Tower - Rezoning Applications, RZ 1998-PR-058 and SEA 83-P-0453, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Tysons Corner - Transit - TACT (Tysons Area Committee on Transportation), 1981 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Tysons Corner - Transit - TTA (Tysons Transportation Association, Inc.), 1982-1983 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Tysons Corner - Transit- Tytran, 1983-1984 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Tysons Corner - Transit- Tytran, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Tysons Corner - Transit- Tytran (2 Transparencies, 85-D-0590, Tysons Cloverleaf), 1985 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Tysons Corner - Transit- Tytran, 1985-1986 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Tysons Corner - Transit- Tytran, 1986-1986 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Tysons Corner - Transit- Tytran, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Tysons Corner - Transit- Tytran, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Tysons Corner - Transit- Tytran "Tysons Corner Map" (3 copies), 1994 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Tysons Corner - Transit - Vienna-Tysons Corner Paratransit System, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Tysons Corner - Transportation - Ramada Road Issues, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Tysons Corner - Transportation - West*Mac Associates, 1990-1991 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Series 7: Washington Metropolitan Area Transportation Files, 1957-2005
  - Transportation - United States. Department of Transportation. Air Quality, 1978, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - United States. National Capital Plannning Commission. Agenda and Related Papers, 1981-1986 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Greater Washington Research Council Materials and Studies (Part 1), 1985-1987 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Greater Washington Research Council Materials and Studies (Part 2), 1985-1987 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments. A Legacy of Excellence for the Washington Region: Task Force Report on Growth and Transportation, 1991 June (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Transportation - Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments - Economic Advisory Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Transportation - Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments - Land Use Policy Committee, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Transportation - Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments - Public Advisory Committee, 1981-1985 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Transportation - Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments - Steering Committee of the Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments' Growth and Transportation Project (Binder), 1992 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments - Transportation Planning Board, Staff Summary Report of the FY73 Long Range Plan for the National Capital Area by Office of Comprehensive Planning, Fairfax County, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments - Transportation Planning Board - Annual Report, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments - Transportation Planning Board, 1983-1984 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments - Transportation Planning Board, 1984-1985 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Transportation - Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments - Transportation Planning Board, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Transportation - Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments - Transportation Planning Board, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Transportation - Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments - Transportation Planning Board, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA; Metro) (Part 1), 1975-1991 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA; Metro) (Part 2), 1977-1979 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Virginia. Department of Highways and Transportation. The VDH&T Communique, 1985-1986 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - Virginia. Department of Transportation. Confronting Virginia's Transportation Challenge: Phase 1 Report of the Commission on Transportation in the Twenty-First Century, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Transportation - Virginia. George Mason University. "Closing the Gap: Proceedings of the Workshop on Alternatives for Funding Transportation in Northern Virginia…" and related materials, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Transportation - Virginia Highway and Transportation Conference, October 19-20, 1978, VMI, Lexington, VA, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Transportation - Northern Virginia Transportation Commission - Annual Report, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Northern Virginia Transportation Commission - John Milliken Materials, 1985-1986, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Northern Virginia Transportation Commission - Minutes, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Northern Virginia Transportation Commission - 1989 Handbook, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - Northern Virginia Transportation Commission - Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Transportation - Northern Virginia Transportation Commission - KPMG Peat Marwick, A Study of Financial Resources for Transportation in Northern Virginia: Final Report: Executive Summary, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Transportation - Northern Virginia Transportation Commission - 1991 Handbook, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Transportation - Airports (Dulles International Airport; Washington National Airport), 1985-1986 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Airports - Airport Noise Abatement, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Airports - Dulles International Airport, 1989-1991 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Bridges - Woodrow Wilson Bridge, 1990-1999 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - I-66 - Extension Inside the Beltway (I-495) (Includes material on Continued Action on Transportation and Environment Inc. (CONTACT), 1973-1979 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - I-66 - Extension Inside the Beltway (I-495), 1975 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - I-66 - Extension Inside the Beltway (I-495), 1976 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - I-66 - Extension Inside the Beltway (I-495), 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - I-66 - Extension Inside the Beltway (I-495), 1979-1982 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - I-66 - Extension Inside the Beltway (I-495), 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - I-66 - "Traffic Management Concepts Interstate 66", 1977 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - I-66 - Continuous Lighting, 1980-1981 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - I-66 - Robert A. Nelson, "A Proposal for I-66." (2 copies), Undated (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - I-66 - U. S. Route 50/I-66 Area Study Task Froce, 1980-1981 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Transportation - Roads - United States - Interstates - I-66 - Carpool/HOV (Theodore Gray material), 1983-1988 (Box 66, Folder 1)